bizzabo.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy - Bizzabo

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) that governs how we, Bizzabo Inc. (“Bizzabo,” “we,” “our" or “us”), use Personal Information (as defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals and/or companies in connection with the use of: (i) the Bizzabo event management service (“Bizzabo Service”), (ii) the website http://www.bizzabo.com, and any other website that we operate (each, together with its sub-domains, content and services, a “Site”); and (iii) the Bizzabo web and mobile service application ("App"); and any other services we provide (each individually, and collectively, the “Service”) – all, as we will provide, develop and enhance from time to time. The Bizzabo Service, Sites, App and any additional Services are individually and collectively referred to herein as the “Services.”

Please read this policy carefully. By clicking "I Agree" or "Next", you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this policy. The use of your personal information under this policy is an integral part of the Services. You are not required by law to provide us your personal information, and therefore providing your information is entirely up to you. However, if you do not provide us the necessary information, we will not be able to provide you with our services. Therefore, if you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or otherwise use the Services.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, to adapt it to changes in our Services, to the way Bizzabo operates, and to regulatory and technological requirements. We will provide a notice about the updated policy within reasonable time in advance to allow you to review the changes and decide whether you wish to continue using the Service. Our notices will be posted, as applicable, on the Site, and we will also send it to you with an email message.

  1. **Introduction.**

We have implemented this Privacy Policy because your privacy, and the privacy of other users, is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way we collect and use your Personal Information in connection with the Services. “Personal Information” means any information that will be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address, a home or other physical address, or other contact information.

  1. **Terms of Use.**

This Privacy Policy forms part of our Bizzabo End User Terms of Service and Organizer Terms which can be viewed on the Site and which you accepted prior to using the Service for the first time (collectively, “Terms”). Any capitalized but undefined term in this Privacy Policy will have the meaning given to it in the Terms.

  1. **What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It.**

We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on the Services. But, we do receive and/or collect Personal Information from you in the following ways:

3.1 **Account.**

To use certain Services, you will be required to create an account (“Account”). We offer different options to create an Account, including

3.2 **"Contact Us" Information.**

If you send us a “Contact Us” request, whether by submitting an online form that we make available or by sending an email to an email address that we display, you will be required to provide us with certain information, such as your name and email address in order to send the message to us. If you wish to contact Bizzabo by regular mail, the updated Bizzabo physical addresses are available at: https://www.bizzabo.com/contact.

3.3 **Share with Friends Service.**

The Services enable you to invite your friends to use our Services by sending them an invitation email message or a text message. You may do so by: (i) using the Services to send or post an invitation message via your Third Party Account; and/or (ii) using the Services to send an invitation email to your friend’s external email address. If you send or post an invitation message, we will store Personal Information about the recipient such as their email address or their third party website account user name and ID.

3.4 **Location Data.**

We provide certain location-based services (“Location Services”) in connection with the Services that are dependent on data related to the geographic location of your mobile device used for the Service (“Location Data”). If you choose to participate in these Location Services, you agree that we will collect or obtain your Location Data. You may use the settings on your mobile device to turn off location-sharing features.

3.5 **Profile.**

Some parts of the Services enable you to build a public profile in connection with your Account (“Public Profile”). Your Public Profile will include your name and other information that you choose to include in your Public Profile, such as your gender and a profile picture, and you can control which such information will appear on your Public Profile. In some cases, even if you do not create a Public Profile, the applicable Event Organizer may create a public profile for you, based on the information you provided while registering for the Services or event, and publish such public profile amongst the profiles of other attendees of such event (the “Event Community”). If you do not want the Event Organizer to create such a public profile for you and publish it automatically within the Event Community, opt out by visiting your Account settings. PLEASE USE CAUTION WHEN UPLOADING CONTENT TO YOUR PUBLIC PROFILE. THE DATA THAT YOU UPLOAD WILL BE AVAILABLE TO OTHERS.

3.6 **Purchases.**

Our Services include the option to purchase certain products or services from us or from Event Organizers or other third parties products and services. If you choose to make a purchase, we will require sufficient information from you to complete the transaction. Such information includes a credit card number and related account and billing information, invoice-related information, and other data required to process the order. We will use the tools and services of third-party service providers to process transactions on our behalf, in which case you acknowledge and agree to our disclosure and transmission of information required to process the transactions and you agree to review and be bound by the terms of use and privacy policy of said third-party service providers. NOTE: WE DO NOT HOLD, USE OR PROCESS YOUR CREDIT CARD DETAILS. THESE DETAILS ARE PROCESSED BY OUR ACCREDITED THIRD-PARTY SERVICES WHO HOLD APPROPRIATE CERTIFICATIONS (PCI-DSS) TO PROCESS THESE DETAILS LAWFULLY.

3.7 **Log Files.**

We will make use of log files. Log files are files automatically generated by our information systems and record system. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We use such information to analyze trends, administer the Services, track users' movements in connection with their use of the Services, and gather demographic information.

3.8 **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.**

Our Services utilize “cookies” -- anonymous identifiers and other tracking technologies -- in order for us to provide our Services and present you with information that is customized for you. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about activity on the Services. Certain cookies and other technologies serve to recall Personal Information, such as an IP address, previously indicated by a user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. NOTE THAT DISABLING COOKIES ON YOUR BROWSER MAY AFFECT YOUR USER EXPERIENCE WITH THE SERVICES.

3.9 **Mobile Device Data.**

We collect limited information from your mobile device in order to provide the Bizzabo Service. Such information includes your mobile device type, mobile device ID, and date and time stamps of Services use. In addition, we deploy analytics technologies within the Service to help us gather aggregate statistics.

  1. **Publicly Available Information.**

Publicly Available Information. Your Public Profile and any publicly available content that you post on or via the Services (“User Submissions”) will be publicly available to other users of the Services and will also be accessed and used by people off the Services. For instance, if you view another user’s profile or "like" a certain event within the Services, such information can be viewed by others. The notices and tools that we provide on the Services should help inform you which information will be made publicly available. If you publish your contact information in any User Submissions or as part of your Public Profile, you may receive unsolicited messages from other users of the Services or the public. WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO ONLY POST INFORMATION THAT YOU ARE SURE YOU WANT TO BE ACCESSIBLE TO ANYONE.

  1. **The Way We Use and Share Personal Information.**

If you submit, or we collect, Personal Information through the Services, then we will use such Personal Information in the following ways:

    1. We will use your Personal Information to provide you with support and assistance in using the Services, and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Services that you are authorized to access.
    2. We will use your designated email address to respond to a “Contact Us” or administrative request (for example, to change your password).
    3. If you choose to send your friend an invitation email or message we will use the contact information that you provide, or make available, to automatically send your friend an invitation email or message. Your name and email address may be included in the invitation email or message.
    4. We will share your Personal Information, and other statistical and analytical information with Event Organizers, for the purpose of providing you with the Services. Event Organizers will use your designated email address to send you updates or news regarding the events you are attending.
    5. We will transfer your Personal Information to our subsidiaries or affiliated companies for the purpose of storing or processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy.
    6. We will share statistical and analytical information with our third-party service providers and partners such as our data hosting providers ("Third-Party Services") to improve our Services.

We also use standard analytics tools of Google Analytics and we will use additional or other analytics tools, from time to time. The privacy practices of these tools are subject to their own privacy policies. The Google Analytics Privacy Policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>.

    7. We will disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of Bizzabo, our users, yourself or the public.
    8. We will use your Personal Information to provide you with features of the Service related to content and interactions and details about other events, in addition to the event that you have registered to.

  1. **Choice and Opting Out.**

You may choose not to receive future promotional, advertising or other Services-related emails from us by selecting an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email that we send. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving the foregoing emails, we will still send you a response to any “Contact Us” request as well as administrative emails (for example, in connection with a password reset request) that are necessary to facilitate your use of the Services. At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide or disclose Personal Information. If you choose not to provide mandatory Personal Information, you may still visit parts of the Services, but you may be unable to access certain options, programs, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

You may use the settings on your mobile device to turn off location-sharing features. If you do not want the Event Organizer to create a public profile for you and publish it automatically within the Event Community, opt out by visiting your Account settings.

  1. **Access/Accuracy.**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate Personal Information. If you would like to delete or correct any of your other Personal Information that we are storing, you may use the tools that we make available on the Services or you may submit an access request by sending an email to support@bizzabo.com. Your email should include adequate details of your request. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will retain certain Personal Information as described in the Data Retention section in this policy. To assist you with your request to access and rectify your personal information, we will need to ask you to provide us certain credentials to make sure that you are who you claim to be. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes). We may redact from the data which we will make available to you, any personal information related to others.

  1. **Links to and Interaction with Third Party Products.**

The Services enable you to interact with or contain links to your Third Party Account and other third party websites and Third Party Services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites or Third Party Services. Please be aware that the Third Party Services may collect Personal Information from you. Accordingly, we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each Third Party Service that you choose to use or interact with.

  1. **Children’s Privacy.**

The Services are not structured to attract and are not intended for use by children under the age of 13 years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at support@bizzabo.com.

  1. **Security.**

The security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to protect the Personal Information submitted to us. These measures and controls are governed by the ISO 27001 information security international standard. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or confidentiality. If you have any questions about security on the Service, you can contact us at support@bizzabo.com.

  1. **Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy.**

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we will transfer or assign your Personal Information in connection with the foregoing events.

  1. **California Privacy Rights.**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to support@bizzabo.com. You can also write to us. Our updated office addresses are published on our "Contact Us" page, at: https://www.bizzabo.com/contact. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.

  1. **Our California Do Not Track Notice.**

We do not currently respond or take any action with respect to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services. We will allow third parties, such as companies that provide us with analytics tools, to collect personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when a consumer uses the Services.

  1. **Transfer Data Outside Your Territory.**

Currently, we store and process information solely in the US, including in sites operated and maintained by cloud-based service providers.

We comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. We have certified to the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/

If you are a resident in a jurisdiction where transfer of your personal information to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you hereby provide us your express and unambiguous consent to such transfer. The data that is transferred will be subject to the Privacy Shield Principles.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact our privacy team at: privacy@bizzabo.com.

We have further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-claim for more information or to file a complaint. These services are provided at no cost to you.

We commit to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by the EU DPAs with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

If your Privacy Shield complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See Privacy Shield Annex 1 at https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction Contact details for the EU data protection authorities can be found at http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about our collection or use of employees’ Personal Information. Current or former employees with inquiries regarding the Privacy Shield or who wish to submit a complaint concerning the handling of their Personal Information should first contact us at: privacy@bizzabo.com. Current or former employees who are not satisfied with the internal resolution of a complaint may seek redress from the panel established by the EU DPAs. We will cooperate in investigations by, and comply with the advice of, the panel with regard to an employee’s Personal Information transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

We are subject to the jurisdiction and enforcement authority of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

We may be liable for the onward transfer of EEA Personal Information to agent third parties pursuant to the Privacy Shield unless we can prove that we were not a party to the actions giving rise to the damage.

  1. **Additional Provisions Related to the Processing of Personal Information Under EU Laws**

If EU data protection laws apply to the processing of your personal information under this policy, then the following additional details apply.

For the purposes of the Services, Bizzabo is a data processor. Bizzabo's data processing addendum, which is available at: https://www.bizzabo.com/privacy/dpa, applies to such processing.

    1. Where we process your personal information as a data controller, then we process your personal information under the following lawful grounds:
      1. Where we process your personal information based on consent, we will ask you to provide us with the appropriate consent.
      2. Performance of our engagements with you and the payment transactions for you.
      3. Protect vital interests of you and of others.
      4. Comply with a legal obligation.
      5. We will further rely on our legitimate interests, which we believe are not overridden by your fundamental rights and freedoms, for the following purposes:

  * Communications with you, including direct marketing where you are our client or a user of our client, or where you make contact with us through our website and other digital assets.
  * Cyber security.
  * Support, customer relations, service operations.
  * Enhancements and improvements to yours and other users' experience with our services.

    1. In addition to the right to access, amendment and deletion of certain information, as described in the "Access/Accuracy" section of this policy, you have the right to:
      1. AT ANY TIME, CONTACT US IF YOU WANT TO WITHDRAW YOUR CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. EXERCISING THIS RIGHT WILL NOT AFFECT THE LAWFULNESS OF PROCESSING BASED ON CONSENT BEFORE ITS WITHDRAWAL AND ON OTHER LAWFUL GROUNDS OF PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.
      2. Request to delete or restrict access to your personal information.
      3. If you exercise one (or more) of the above-mentioned rights, in accordance with the provisions of applicable law, you may request to be informed that third parties that hold your personal information, in accordance with this Policy, will act accordingly.
      4. You may ask to transfer your personal information in accordance with your right to data portability.
      5. You may object to the processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
      6. You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affecting you.
      7. You have a right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the EU data protection laws.

A summary and further details about your rights under EU data protection laws, is available on the EU Commission's website at:https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/rights-citizens_en.

    1. If you are registered for an event through our services, then for the purposes of EU data protection laws, our processing of your personal data under this policy are made on behalf of the Event Organizer. Accordingly, for these purposes, the Event Organizer is the data controller and Bizzabo is the data processor.
    2. To apply for exercising your above rights in relation to the processing of your personal information in relation with a specific event, you should contact first the Event Organizer with your request. We will follow the Event Organizer's instructions.
    3. To exercise the above rights, you will need to provide sufficient credentials to authenticate your identify, your location and identify data relevant to you on our information systems and will further ask you questions to understand the nature and scope of your request.
    4. Your requests may be accepted or denied, in accordance with considerations and provisions in applicable laws.

If we need to delete data following your request, it will take some time until we completely delete residual copies of the data from our active servers and from our backup systems. If you have any concerns about the way we process your personal information, you are welcome to contact our privacy team at: privacy@bizzabo.com. We will look into your inquiry and make good-faith efforts to respond promptly.

  1. **Date Retention.**

As long as you use the Service, we will keep information about you, unless we are required by law to delete it, or if we decide to remove it at our discretion. At any time, you can remove data from your public profile, delete your account altogether, or request us to delete your data pursuant to your rights under this policy. We retain different types of information for different periods, depending on the purposes of processing such information, our legitimate business purposes as well as pursuant to legal requirements under the applicable law such as for tax related requirements, for accounts settling, record keeping, archiving and other legal issues for 90 days after we complete our engagement with the Event Organizer. We will also retain and use your identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements for 90 days after we complete our engagement with the Event Organizer. In addition, after you delete your identifiable information, residual copies will remain in our backup systems for a certain period of time before they are deleted from our active servers. This deletion of your data will not change or delete identifiable information which may have already been shared with third parties, as permitted in this Privacy Policy or any other agreement between you and us. Other information that we do not need to maintain, will be removed following the termination of the agreement with the relevant Event Organizer. We will keep aggregated non-identifiable information without limitation, and to the extent reasonable we will delete or de-identify potentially identifiable information, when we no longer need to process the information.

  1. **Commitment.**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Service to meet these demands. If you have any comments, concerns about the way we process your personal information or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@bizzabo.com.
